{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775227587","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775227587"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 2aa63cb1-3253-498b-9f1e-7be9c8e4fe80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775231300","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775231299"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 2aa63cb1-3253-498b-9f1e-7be9c8e4fe80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775238847","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775238847"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 2aa63cb1-3253-498b-9f1e-7be9c8e4fe80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775248259","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775248258"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 2aa63cb1-3253-498b-9f1e-7be9c8e4fe80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775260702","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775260701"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 2aa63cb1-3253-498b-9f1e-7be9c8e4fe80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775274125","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775274125"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 2aa63cb1-3253-498b-9f1e-7be9c8e4fe80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775280862","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775280862"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 2aa63cb1-3253-498b-9f1e-7be9c8e4fe80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775286704","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775286704"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 2aa63cb1-3253-498b-9f1e-7be9c8e4fe80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775334118","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775334118"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 55de86e1-acb3-48d3-9f55-665f25d4765f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pamoja_kubwa-pamoja-kubwa-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" pamoja"," userResponse":" hadithi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775338775","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775338775"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 55de86e1-acb3-48d3-9f55-665f25d4765f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pamoja_kubwa-pamoja-kubwa-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" pamoja"," userResponse":" kubwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775341989","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775341989"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 55de86e1-acb3-48d3-9f55-665f25d4765f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pamoja_kubwa-pamoja-kubwa-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" pamoja"," userResponse":" pamoja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775387434","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775387434"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 55de86e1-acb3-48d3-9f55-665f25d4765f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kucha_kuzaliwa-i-tambarare-kucha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kucha"," userResponse":" kucha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775413580","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775413580"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 55de86e1-acb3-48d3-9f55-665f25d4765f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku_usiku-mtoto-kubwa-wapi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" usiku"," userResponse":" wapi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775418524","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775418524"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 55de86e1-acb3-48d3-9f55-665f25d4765f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku_usiku-mtoto-kubwa-wapi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" usiku"," userResponse":" mtoto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775421977","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775421977"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 55de86e1-acb3-48d3-9f55-665f25d4765f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku_usiku-mtoto-kubwa-wapi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" usiku"," userResponse":" usiku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775486234","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775486232"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 55de86e1-acb3-48d3-9f55-665f25d4765f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" usiku_usiku-mtoto-kubwa-wapi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775486349","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775486349"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 55de86e1-acb3-48d3-9f55-665f25d4765f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775495236","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775495236"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 55de86e1-acb3-48d3-9f55-665f25d4765f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.rise.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775504348","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775504348"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 55de86e1-acb3-48d3-9f55-665f25d4765f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775510271","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775510270"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 55de86e1-acb3-48d3-9f55-665f25d4765f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775520793","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775520793"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775521016","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775521016"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775521980","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775521980"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775523262","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775523262"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775526178","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775526178"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775527035","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775527034"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775527366","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775527365"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775528611","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775528611"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775532213","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775532213"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775533212","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775533210"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775533470","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775533470"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775534428","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775534428"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775537287","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775537287"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775538327","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775538326"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775538811","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775538809"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775543422","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775543422"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775543532","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775543532"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 8ee6effd-c1c9-4dae-bce0-1f9c8420ad2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775563421","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775563421"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 5d9d1a7b-1d99-4206-b4e6-dc98238a46b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_h_s"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775570076","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775570076"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 5d9d1a7b-1d99-4206-b4e6-dc98238a46b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_s_l"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775576744","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775576744"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 5d9d1a7b-1d99-4206-b4e6-dc98238a46b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_l_g"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775583392","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775583392"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 5d9d1a7b-1d99-4206-b4e6-dc98238a46b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_s_n"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775590060","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775590060"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 5d9d1a7b-1d99-4206-b4e6-dc98238a46b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_i_z"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775596734","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775596734"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 5d9d1a7b-1d99-4206-b4e6-dc98238a46b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_i_s"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775603401","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775603401"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 5d9d1a7b-1d99-4206-b4e6-dc98238a46b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_w_i"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775610102","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775610102"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 5d9d1a7b-1d99-4206-b4e6-dc98238a46b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_s_l"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775616748","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775616748"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 5d9d1a7b-1d99-4206-b4e6-dc98238a46b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_d_s"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775623495","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775623494"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 5d9d1a7b-1d99-4206-b4e6-dc98238a46b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_o_s"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775635162","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775635162"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" 5d9d1a7b-1d99-4206-b4e6-dc98238a46b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_t_o_s"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775709538","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775709537"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" ac76fbfd-f265-425f-83b1-3d32c9892242"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_h_s"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775715776","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775715775"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212654"," gameId":" ac76fbfd-f265-425f-83b1-3d32c9892242"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_u_h_s"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}